smithfield.com 2018-12-27

# Smithfield Foods, Inc. Privacy Policy & Company Use of Information

**Privacy Policy**

This website and any related websites, microsites, mobile applications and social media platforms (each, a “Site” and collectively, our “Sites”) is owned and operated by Smithfield Foods, Inc. or one of its subsidiary companies (collectively, “Smithfield”). Smithfield knows your privacy and security are important, so we are very sensitive to the privacy concerns of those who use our Sites.

This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect and use information about you through your use of the Sites and with whom we may share it. The Privacy Policy also describes the measures we take to protect the security of your personal information and how you can contact us to update your preferences regarding how we communicate with you or answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices.

By accessing and using this Site you agree to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice by posting the modified Privacy Policy here. You should check this Privacy Policy each time you visit the Site to identify and understand any changes made since your previous visit. By continuing to access or use the Site, you agree to be bound by any modifications to this Privacy Policy. Please consult the Site _Terms of Use_ for additional terms and conditions that apply to your access and use of the Site.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

This Site is not aimed at children under 13 years of age. Any information submitted through the Site that we know or reasonably believe originated from a child under 13 years of age will be deleted. Children should never reveal their address, phone number or other personal information to any strangers on the Internet.

**_Information We Collect and How We Use It_**

**Information You Provide Directly to Us**

When you participate in or register on the Site for promotions, offers, programs, contests, or sweepstakes, or otherwise communicate with us, you may directly provide us with certain information, including, but not limited to, the following types of personal information:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Postal address
  * Gender
  * Marital status
  * Demographic information
  * Income Level
  * Age or birthdate
  * Family or household information
  * Information about your interests, hobbies, product preferences, or shopping activities
  * Information you affirmatively allow a third party service, such as Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram, to provide to us.

We may also offer you the opportunity to sign up for email newsletters and other communications and promotional materials **.   **We may collect your name, email address, zip code, state and other information for purposes of sending those communications. ** **

**Information We Collect from Social Networking Services**

If you choose to access or use social networking services, such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, etc., we may receive certain personal information that you make available to those services, including, without limitation, information about your contacts on those services. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of each social networking service you use to understand how your information may be used and shared by the service or third parties and to set your privacy settings on those services in accordance with your preferences.

**Information We Collect by Automated Means When You Visit Our Sites**

When you visit any of our Sites, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, web server logs, web beacons, or other technologies that collect information about your computer or device and your online activity.

Please note that our Sites or website service providers may not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, such as “do not track” instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. Cookies are files that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings in your browser. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of the Site.

In conjunction with the gathering of information through cookies, our web servers may log information such as your device type, operating system type, browser type, domain and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. The web server logs also may record information such as the address of the web page that referred you to the Site and the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. They may also log information about your interaction with the Site, such as which pages you visit, links you click and the items you view. To control which web servers collect information by automated means, we may place tags on our web pages called “web beacons,” which are small files that link web pages to particular web servers and their cookies.

We also may use third party web analytics services on the Site, such as those of Google Analytics, ShareThis, or other analytics services. These service providers use cookies, web beacons and other technology to help us analyze how users use the Site. The information collected by the cookies and web beacons (including your IP address) will be disclosed to these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Site. To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, you may visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>_._ To learn more about opting out of ShareThis, you may visit <http://sharethis.com/privacy.>

**Information We Obtain from Other Sources  
**We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, data aggregators and information collected from other brands or businesses in the Smithfield family of companies. This information may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, age, gender, marital status, income level, demographic information, purchasing behavior, interests, hobbies, product preferences, online activity, or any other publicly available information.

**How We May Use Information  
**We may use any information we collect on or through the Site, from other commercial sources, or in connection with a promotion, offer, contest, sweepstake, or social networking service, to operate, evaluate and improve our business, products, services and Sites, to communicate with you and provide information to you regarding our products, services and promotions, and to customize and optimize your experience on the Site. We also may use information we collect in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

Other specific ways we may use this information include, without limitation, the following:

  * To provide you with information about our products, services, and promotions
  * To enable you to use certain features of the Site
  * To verify your identity and respond to your comments or questions about our products, services, promotions, or company
  * To process and fulfill your online purchases
  * To register you for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions for which you have requested to be registered and to administer such contests, sweepstakes or promotions
  * To better understand our customers and product needs
  * To provide you with services or offers you have requested
  * To help us develop new and improved products, services, promotions and websites
  * To conduct market research, analysis and data analytics
  * To determine the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing
  * To analyze our products, services, promotions and websites
  * To administer, manage and optimize our Sites
  * To prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and liabilities
  * To perform accounting, audit, billing reconciliation and collection activities
  * To manage risk exposure and quality
  * To comply with or enforce legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and terms.

**Sharing of Information  
**We may share information we collect or that you provide to us on or through the Site, or in connection with a promotion, offer, contest, sweepstakes, or social networking service, with our service providers and licensees who perform services on our behalf. These service providers and licensees are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. We also may share information with our affiliated companies, licensees, franchisees, advertising agencies and promotional partners to, for example, send you information about products, services, or promotions that may interest you.

We also may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided to us in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy.

**User-Generated Content  
**Certain features on our Site may contain interactive areas where users can submit comments, images, recipes, or other content that may be visible to others. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., name, email address, postal address, etc.) in public, interactive sections of the Site, the information can be read and used by others. We strongly encourage you to not disclose any personally identifiable information in any such submissions of content to the Site. We make no representations and undertake no obligations as to the security or use of information you voluntarily submit via any Sites. We also reserve the right to remove any user-generated content we deem inappropriate for any reason in our sole discretion and without notice.

**Links to Other Websites  
**The Site may contain links to other websites that are owned or operated by companies other than Smithfield or any of its affiliated companies. Linked websites may have their own privacy policies and are not governed by this Privacy Policy. We strongly suggest you carefully review the privacy policies, practices and terms of use for all websites you visit through a link on our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any websites owned and operated by third parties.

**How We Protect Personal Information  
**We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards customary in the industry to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. While we believe these safeguards are effective to secure your personal information, no method of security is 100% secure from all potential threats. Consequently, we cannot guarantee the absolute safety of personal information submitted on the Site.

**Notice to California Residents  
**If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your information with certain affiliates and other third parties for their own marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as specified in the _How to Contact Us_ section below. Your opt-out will be effective until you revoke it. Your opt-out will only affect the future sharing of information and will not be retroactive

**Your Control Over Your Information  
**You may contact us as described in the _How to Contact Us_ section below to review and update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, or to submit a request. All of our promotional emails contain an “unsubscribe” link that you can click through to stop receiving future promotional emails from the Smithfield brand or group that originated the promotion.  Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, Smithfield will still send you messages about your questions and purchases.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have questions or comments about our products, services, or company, please contact us by using the Contact form available at [www.smithfield.com/contact](http://www.smithfield.com/contact). For specific questions or concerns about the terms of our Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us by using the Contact form or by emailing Smithfield at [privacypolicy@smithfield.com](mailto:privacypolicy@smithfield.com).
